Meat! Sausage.
Hey ... I said meat... not meat... last week... and now that the fire was lit last week, we're going to cook some meat!
Yes!
Let's cook some meat!
Oh!
Yes!
I'm going to cook the meat!
I'm afraid the meat will fly away while it's cooking, with the wind.
I hope it's okay.
Okay.
Flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap.
I was going to put half of something else on it.
Oh, well...
Oh, my God.
It's too windy.
I really want it to blow.
I just want it to blow, you know? I hope this doesn't blow the meat away. Ohhhh... .... I want to grill some sausages, but I wonder if they'll roll around in the wind?
I'm worried about that.
What do you think? What do you guys think?
Do you think they'll roll?
Let's grill them first.
What? What? I'm feeling pretty good already. Isn't it too soon? That's why we're doing it.
It's already good, but it's hot.
Tonka has to buy it.
That looks good.
I have to buy some Tonka.
I gotta get some tonka.
Tonka.
It's totally important.
No, thank you.
What's better than this?
I bought it to replace the shula cups.
I didn't buy a flat plate.
I'm not sure if I'm going to dig this in hot water, or sour, but it's just right.
And I didn't buy any right now.
Nice timing.
What?
Looks super yummy.
Wow.
It smells like summer.
Barbecue.
Barbecue sounds like summer.
I didn't buy it.
I smell summer... barbecue... summer...
Barbecue.
Barbecue smells like summer.
I don't know, it's just my idea of summer.
Summer.
The moment I put these on, I couldn't hold the chopsticks.
The moment I put these on, I couldn't hold the chopsticks at all.
Oh, no!
It looks so delicious!
A little more work on this and it'll be ready.
Ta-da!
The meat is done! Looks really good!
This chicken looks like it's done just right.
It looks like it's going to be grilled!
Let's try it!
Let's go!
I need a flat plate!
Oh!
Oh, wow.
Wow!
What's that... thing on the lake?
Oh, my God! It's running! Bon appétit!
Very, very, very oishii delicious! I'm so happy! This is happy time!
Delicious? Very very delicious!
It's delicious in Indonesian!
Very good.
Happy.
It's so good!
Let's cook sausages too!
Let's cook some sausages!
Next
Sausage!
So happy!
I have to take care of this so it doesn't roll away.
23, I have to take care of it.
This one's cute.
Here, take this.
It's delicious.Delicious.
Very good.
I think you can use it at home, too.
If you see it, buy it.
It's really got everything.
I can take the snow and stuff with me, and it's all gone.
Almost there.
It's gonna get warmer.
Oh, I'm getting some nice color.
Oh! Oh, look out!
I can't wait to eat it.
Let's go down.
Is there anything you guys definitely cook on the barbecue? Is there meat? I'm sure there is.
Oh, my God! Burnt!
But sometimes it tastes better when it's burnt like this!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
It's so good! It's basil and lemon, I'm so happy! It's too good! I'm so jealous that you all came.
I know, we ran out of time. I know, I know, I'm a food snob.
I'm so sorry.
It's so good!
Sorry ....... I grilled some meat and sausages... can't wait to see what you cook next time... bye bye bye...